<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Federal Regulatory Comment Periods</title><link>https://your-username.github.io/federal-regulatory-comment-bot/</link><description>Open comment periods for federal regulations</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:26:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>FWS: Implementation of the Pittman-Robertson Wildlife Restoration and Dingell-Johnson Sport Fish Restoration Acts</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FWS-HQ-OCI-2025-0080-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;This direct final rule (DFR) rescinds portions of the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service's (Service) regulations containing general provisions related to requirements for programs and subprograms authorized under the Pittman-Robertson Wildlife Restoration Act and the Dingell-Johnson Sport Fish Restoration Act. This DFR removes redundancies and eliminates superfluous sections. These recissions will result in regulations that better serve the American public, streamline government operations, and increase efficiencies for recipients of our financial assistance programs.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FWS-HQ-OCI-2025-0080-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">FWS-HQ-OCI-2025-0080-0001</guid></item><item><title>DOC: Removing Redundant, Obsolete, and Inefficient Provisions from the Regulations Governing Restrictions on Lobbying</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/DOC_FRDOC_0001-0102</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Department of Commerce ("Commerce") is proposing to amend its regulations governing restrictions on lobbying. Specifically, Commerce is proposing to remove two redundant and unnecessary compliance provisions and remove two reporting requirements that are obsolete and unwarranted. This action is necessary to reduce regulatory complexity and streamline the regulations governing restrictions on lobbying. The intended effects of this action are to eliminate redundancy, promote administrative efficiency, and update Commerce's lobbying regulations to properly reflect and implement the underlying statutory authority in its current form.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/DOC_FRDOC_0001-0102"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">DOC_FRDOC_0001-0102</guid></item><item><title>EPA: Air Quality State Implementation Plans; Approvals and Promulgations: California; Coachella Valley; 1997 Ozone Standards; Determination of Attainment by the Attainment Date</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA-R09-OAR-2025-3127-0048</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is proposing to determine that the Riverside County (Coachella Valley) 1997 ozone Extreme nonattainment area ("Coachella Valley") attained the 1997 ozone national ambient air quality standards (NAAQS) by its June 15, 2025, attainment date. This proposed determination is based on quality- assured and certified ambient air quality monitoring data from 2022 through 2024. We are taking comments on this proposal and plan to follow with a final action.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA-R09-OAR-2025-3127-0048"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">EPA-R09-OAR-2025-3127-0048</guid></item><item><title>FWS: Public Access, Use, and Recreation for Four National Wildlife Refuges</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FWS-HQ-NWRS-2025-0083-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;This direct final rule removes certain regulations related to enforcement of various activities on Havasu National Wildlife Refuge, Pond Creek National Wildlife Refuge, St. Vincent National Wildlife Refuge, and Upper Mississippi River National Wildlife and Fish Refuge. Specifically, the rescinded regulations relate to activities such as use of fireworks, damaging vegetation, dogs that disturb wildlife or habitat, use of firearms and other weapons, littering, alcohol use, and boat speed. These regulations are redundant and therefore can be rescinded without adverse impact.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FWS-HQ-NWRS-2025-0083-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">FWS-HQ-NWRS-2025-0083-0001</guid></item><item><title>EPA: Updating the Water Quality Certification Regulations</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA-HQ-OW-2025-2929-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is publishing this proposed rule to update and clarify several substantive and procedural requirements for water quality certification under Clean Water Act (CWA or the Act) section 401. CWA section 401 is a direct grant of authority to States (and Tribes that have been approved for "treatment as a State" status) to review for compliance with appropriate Federal, State, and Tribal water quality requirements any discharge into waters of the United States that may result from a proposed activity that requires a Federal license or permit. This proposed rule is intended to clarify several aspects of the certification process consistent with the statutory framework.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA-HQ-OW-2025-2929-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">EPA-HQ-OW-2025-2929-0001</guid></item><item><title>MARAD: Use of Foreign-Built Small Passenger Vessel in United States Coastwise Trade: M/V Halve Maan II</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/MARAD-2026-0001-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Secretary of Transportation, as represented by MARAD, is authorized to make determinations regarding the coastwise use of foreign built; certain U.S. built; and U.S. and foreign rebuilt vessels that solely carry no more than twelve passengers for hire. MARAD has received such a determination request and is publishing this notice to solicit comments to assist with determining whether the proposed use of the vessel set forth in the request would have an adverse effect on U.S. vessel builders or U.S. coastwise trade businesses that use U.S.- built vessels in those businesses. Information about the requestor's vessel, including a description of the proposed service, is in the SUPPLEMENTARY INFORMATION section below.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/MARAD-2026-0001-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">MARAD-2026-0001-0001</guid></item><item><title>DOS: Agency Information Collection Activities; Proposals, Submissions, and Approvals: Eligibility Questionnaire for HAVANA Act Payments</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/DOS_FRDOC_0001-7031</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Department of State has submitted the information collection described below to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for approval. In accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995 we are requesting comments on this collection from all interested individuals and organizations. The purpose of this Notice is to allow 30 days for public comment.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/DOS_FRDOC_0001-7031"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">DOS_FRDOC_0001-7031</guid></item><item><title>VA: Privacy Act; Systems of Records (FR Doc No: 2026-00725)</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA-2026-VACO-0001-0014</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-15T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;As required by the Privacy Act of 1974, notice is hereby given that the Department of Veterans Affairs (VA) is rescinding the system of records (SOR) known as "The Office of Inspector General Management Information System (MIS)--VA" (71VA53), which consists of records and information about the Office of Inspector General (OIG) employees for various management and human resources objectives. DATES: Comments on this rescinded SOR must be received no later than 30 days after publication in the Federal Register. If no public comment is received during the period allowed for comment or unless otherwise published in the Federal Register by VA, the rescindment will become effective a minimum of 30 days after the date of publication in the Federal Register. If VA receives public comments, VA shall review the comments to determine whether any changes to the notice are necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA-2026-VACO-0001-0014"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">VA-2026-VACO-0001-0014</guid></item><item><title>VA: Privacy Act; Systems of Records (FR Doc No: 2026-00726)</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA-2026-VACO-0001-0013</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-15T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;As required by the Privacy Act of 1974, notice is hereby given that VA is amending the system of records titled "Veterans, Dependents of Veterans, and VA Beneficiary Survey Records--VA" (43VA008) as set forth in the Federal Register. This system is used to collect data regarding the characteristics of America's Veteran, Service member, family member, and beneficiary populations through surveys that may be augmented with information from several existing VA systems of records and with information from non-VA sources.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA-2026-VACO-0001-0013"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">VA-2026-VACO-0001-0013</guid></item><item><title>VA: Privacy Act; Systems of Records (FR Doc No: 2026-00682)</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA-2026-VACO-0001-0012</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-15T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In accordance with the Privacy Act of 1974, the Department of Veterans Affairs (VA) is modifying the systems of records listed in this notice to incorporate one routine use related to the disclosure of records to the U.S. Department of the Treasury pursuant to the Office of Management and Budget's Memorandum 25-32. The new routine use permits disclosures of records to the U.S. Department of the Treasury when the information is relevant to review payment and award eligibility through the Do Not Pay Working System for the purposes of identifying, preventing, or recouping improper payments to an applicant for, or recipient of, Federal funds. For full descriptions of the systems of records, please see the chart below for a list of the System of Records Notices (SORNs) and their corresponding Federal Register citations.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA-2026-VACO-0001-0012"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">VA-2026-VACO-0001-0012</guid></item><item><title>EIB: Application for Final Commitment for a Long-Term Loan or Financial Guarantee in Excess of100 Million Dollars</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EIB_FRDOC_0001-0853</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-10T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;This Notice is to inform the public, in accordance with Section 3(c)(10) of the Export-Import Bank Act of 1945, as amended (12 U.S.C. 635a(c)(10)), the Export-Import Bank of the United States ("EXIM") has received an application for final commitment for a long- term loan or financial guarantee in excess of $100 million. Comments received within the comment period specified below will be presented to the EXIM Board of Directors prior to final action on this Transaction.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EIB_FRDOC_0001-0853"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">EIB_FRDOC_0001-0853</guid></item><item><title>BSC: FMCF-1_FFM Functions and Activities_Release FY2027</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/BSC-FFM-2026-0001-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-31T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/BSC-FFM-2026-0001-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">BSC-FFM-2026-0001-0001</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 1. TERREPOWER LLC HTSUS 9032.90.6120</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0001</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 5. TERREPOWER LLC HTSUS 3917.40.0095</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0005</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0005"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0005</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 8. TERREPOWER LLC HTSUS 8412.21.0075</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0008</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0008"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0008</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 11. I-PEX USA Manufacturing Inc. HTSIS 7326.90.90.90</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0011</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0011"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0011</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 2. TERREPOWER LLC HTSUS 9032.90.6120</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0002</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0002"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0002</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 7. TERREPOWER LLC HTSUS 8421.29.0015</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0007</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0007"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0007</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 4. TERREPOWER LLC HTSUS 8708.99.8180</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0004</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0004"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0004</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 3. TERREPOWER LLC HTSUS 9032.10.0090</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0003</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0003"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0003</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 9. TERREPOWER LLC HTSUS 8481.20.0050</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0009</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0009"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0009</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 6. TERREPOWER LLC HTSUS 8708.99.8180</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0006</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0006"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0006</guid></item><item><title>ITA: Submission 10. IHI Turbo America HTSUS 8414.90.4165 and 8414.90.4190</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0010</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ITA-2025-0039-0010"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ITA-2025-0039-0010</guid></item><item><title>VA: Agency Information Collection Activities; Proposals, Submissions, and Approvals: Gray Market Clauses</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA_FRDOC_0001-6993</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-03-18T03:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Office of Acquisition and Logistics (OAL), Department of Veterans Affairs (VA), is announcing an opportunity for public comment on the proposed collection of certain information by the agency. Under the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA) of 1995, Federal agencies are required to publish notice in the Federal Register concerning each proposed collection of information, including each proposed extension of a currently approved collection, and allow 60 days for public comment in response to the notice.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA_FRDOC_0001-6993"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">VA_FRDOC_0001-6993</guid></item><item><title>FAA: Agency Information Collection Activities; Proposals, Submissions, and Approvals: Operations Specifications, Part 129 Application</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FAA-2025-0703-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-03-18T03:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995, FAA invites public comments about our intention to request the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) approval to renew information collection. The FAA assesses the information collected and issues operations specifications to foreign air carriers. These operations specifications assure the foreign air carrier's ability to navigate and communicate safely within the U.S. National Airspace System.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FAA-2025-0703-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">FAA-2025-0703-0001</guid></item><item><title>FHWA: Agency Information Collection Activities; Proposals, Submissions, and Approvals</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FHWA-2026-0001-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-03-18T03:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The FHWA invites public comments about our intention to request the Office of Management and Budget's (OMB) approval for three new information collections, which are summarized below under SUPPLEMENTARY INFORMATION. We are required to publish this notice in the Federal Register by the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FHWA-2026-0001-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">FHWA-2026-0001-0001</guid></item><item><title>DEA: 2026-00833</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/DEA-2026-0100-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-03-18T03:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Siegfried USA, LLC has applied to be registered as a bulk manufacturer of basic class(es) of controlled substance(s). Refer to Supplementary Information listed below for further drug information.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/DEA-2026-0100-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">DEA-2026-0100-0001</guid></item><item><title>USCIS: Improving Continuity for Religious Organizations and Their Employees</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/USCIS-2025-0403-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-03-18T03:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;This interim final rule (IFR) amends U.S. Department of Homeland Security (DHS) regulations to remove the requirement that R-1 religious workers who have reached the maximum period of stay must reside abroad and be physically present outside the United States for one year before being eligible for readmission in R-1 status after departing from the United States upon reaching the maximum admission period. The purpose of this change is to promote stability and minimize disruptions to the vital services that R-1 religious workers provide to U.S. churches, mosques, synagogues, and other bona fide nonprofit religious organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/USCIS-2025-0403-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">USCIS-2025-0403-0001</guid></item><item><title>VA: Agency Information Collection Activities; Proposals, Submissions, and Approvals: Department of Veterans Affairs Acquisition Regulation—Information Security and Privacy Contract Clauses</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA_FRDOC_0001-6992</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-03-18T03:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Office of Acquisition and Logistics (OAL), Department of Veterans Affairs (VA), is announcing an opportunity for public comment on the proposed collection of certain information by the agency. Under the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA) of 1995, Federal agencies are required to publish notice in the Federal Register concerning each proposed collection of information, including each proposed extension of a currently approved collection, and allow 60 days for public comment in response to the notice.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/VA_FRDOC_0001-6992"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">VA_FRDOC_0001-6992</guid></item><item><title>CDC: Maritime Activity Illness and Death Reporting</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/CDC-2025-1047-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-03-17T03:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/CDC-2025-1047-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">CDC-2025-1047-0001</guid></item><item><title>CDC: Poison Center Collaborations for Public Health Emergencies</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/CDC-2025-1014-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-03-17T03:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/CDC-2025-1014-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">CDC-2025-1014-0001</guid></item><item><title>FAA: Airworthiness Directives: Airbus Helicopters</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FAA-2026-0011-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-03-03T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The FAA is superseding Airworthiness Directive (AD) 2025-23- 52, which applied to all Airbus Helicopters Model EC130B4 and EC130T2 helicopters. AD 2025-23-52, required replacing the center shaft assembly with a serviceable center shaft assembly (either a shaft with another part number (P/N) or the same P/N with lower hours time-in- service (TIS)) and prohibited installing a center shaft assembly that is not a serviceable center shaft assembly on any helicopter. Since the FAA issued AD 2025-23-52, it was determined that for certain center shaft assemblies a repetitive inspection is adequate instead of replacement. This AD requires repetitively inspecting the center shaft assembly for cracks and replacing the center shaft assembly if it fails the inspection or exceeds a certain TIS. This AD also prohibits installing a center shaft assembly that is not a serviceable center shaft assembly on any helicopter. The FAA is issuing this AD to address the unsafe condition on these products.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FAA-2026-0011-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">FAA-2026-0011-0001</guid></item><item><title>FAA: Airworthiness Directives: The Boeing Company Airplanes; Correction</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FAA-2025-5403-0003</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-24T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The FAA is correcting a notice of proposed rulemaking (NPRM) that was published in the Federal Register. The NPRM proposed to issue an airworthiness directive (AD) that would apply to certain The Boeing Company Model 737-600, -700, -700C, -800, -900, and -900ER series airplanes. As published, the docket number referenced throughout the NPRM is incorrect. This document corrects that error. In all other respects, the original document remains the same; however, for clarity, the FAA is publishing the entire proposed rule in the Federal Register.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FAA-2025-5403-0003"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">FAA-2025-5403-0003</guid></item><item><title>NRC: Information Collection: Cooperation With States at Commercial Nuclear Power Plants and Other Nuclear Production and Utilization Facilities</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/NRC-2024-0211-0005</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) has recently submitted a request for renewal of an existing collection of information to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review. The information collection is entitled, "Cooperation With States at Commercial Nuclear Power Plants and Other Nuclear Production and Utilization Facilities."&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/NRC-2024-0211-0005"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">NRC-2024-0211-0005</guid></item><item><title>OSM: Regulatory Program: Wyoming</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/OSM_FRDOC_0001-0406</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;We, the Office of Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement (OSMRE), are announcing receipt of a proposed rule amendment to the Wyoming regulatory program (Wyoming program) under the Surface Mining Control and Reclamation Act of 1977 (SMCRA or the Act). Between 2017 and 2021, the Wyoming Environmental Quality Council (EQC) approved several changes to the Wyoming Department of Environmental Quality (WYDEQ) Rules of Practice and Procedure. These updates largely focused on "Contested Case Hearings" rules and regulations for Wyoming State agencies. Accordingly, the State submitted this amendment proposal to OSMRE on its own initiative.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/OSM_FRDOC_0001-0406"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">OSM_FRDOC_0001-0406</guid></item><item><title>SSA: Privacy Act; Systems of Records</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/SSA-2025-0035-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In accordance with the Privacy Act of 1974, we are issuing public notice of our intent to modify an existing system of records entitled, Requests for Accommodation from Members of the Public (60- 0378), last published in full on June 17, 2014. This notice publishes details of the modified system as set forth below under the caption, SUPPLEMENTARY INFORMATION.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/SSA-2025-0035-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">SSA-2025-0035-0001</guid></item><item><title>HUD: Privacy Act; Systems of Records</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/HUD-2026-0067-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Under the Privacy Act of 1974, as amended, the Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) is issuing a public notice of its intent to modify the HUD System of Records Notices for the HUD systems of records listed below.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/HUD-2026-0067-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">HUD-2026-0067-0001</guid></item><item><title>EPA: Proposed Settlement Agreement, Stipulation, Order, and Judgment, etc.: CERCLA Cost Recovery Settlement for the Trinseo Polymer Release Site, Bristol, Bucks County, PA</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA_FRDOC_0001-32510</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In accordance with section 122(i) of the Comprehensive Environmental Response, Compensation, and Liability Act of 1980 (CERCLA), notice is hereby given by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Region 3, of a proposed cost recovery settlement agreement (Settlement) pursuant to CERCLA with Altuglas, LLC (Settling Party) relating to the Trinseo Polymer Release Site (Site), located in Bristol, Bucks County, Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA_FRDOC_0001-32510"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">EPA_FRDOC_0001-32510</guid></item><item><title>PHMSA: Permits; Applications, Issuances, etc.: Hazardous Materials</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/PHMSA-2013-0008-0642</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In accordance with the procedures governing the application for, and the processing of, special permits from the Department of Transportation's Hazardous Material Regulations, notice is hereby given that the Office of Hazardous Materials Safety has granted or denied the application described herein.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/PHMSA-2013-0008-0642"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">PHMSA-2013-0008-0642</guid></item><item><title>FDA: Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for Office of Management and Budget Review; Comment Request; Warning Plans for Certain Tobacco Products</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FDA-2025-N-0956-0002</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) is announcing that a proposed collection of information has been submitted to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and clearance under the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FDA-2025-N-0956-0002"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">FDA-2025-N-0956-0002</guid></item><item><title>FMCSA: Exemption Application: Parts and Accessories Necessary for Safe Operation; Charles Machine Works, Inc.</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FMCSA-2019-0069-0009</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Federal Motor Carrier Safety Administration (FMCSA) requests public comment on an application from Charles Machine Works, Inc. (CMW), a wholly owned subsidiary of The Toro Company, seeking renewal of a 5-year exemption from the Agency's prohibition against the use of gravity-fed or siphon-fed fuel systems on commercial motor vehicles (CMVs). The exemption would allow CMW's CMVs equipped with certain auxiliary equipment to use gravity-fed or siphon-fed fuel systems when the auxiliary equipment is operated only while the CMV is stationary. FMCSA requests public comment on CMW's application for renewal of this exemption.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/FMCSA-2019-0069-0009"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">FMCSA-2019-0069-0009</guid></item><item><title>EPA: Agency Information Collection Activities; Proposals, Submissions, and Approvals: Brownfields Program—Accomplishment Reporting in Assessment, Cleanup and Redevelopment Exchange System</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA-HQ-OLEM-2024-0477-0027</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) has submitted an information collection request (ICR), Brownfields Program-- Accomplishment Reporting in Assessment, Cleanup and Redevelopment Exchange System (EPA ICR Number 2104.10, OMB Control Number 2050-0192) to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and approval in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act. This is a proposed revision of the ICR, which is currently approved through March 31, 2026. Public comments were previously requested via the Federal Register on October 25, 2024 during a 60-day comment period. This notice allows for an additional 30 days for public comments.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA-HQ-OLEM-2024-0477-0027"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">EPA-HQ-OLEM-2024-0477-0027</guid></item><item><title>PHMSA: Permits; Applications, Issuances, etc.: Hazardous Materials</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/PHMSA-2013-0008-0641</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In accordance with the procedures governing the application for, and the processing of, special permits from the Department of Transportation's Hazardous Material Regulations, notice is hereby given that the Office of Hazardous Materials Safety has received the application described herein.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/PHMSA-2013-0008-0641"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">PHMSA-2013-0008-0641</guid></item><item><title>DOL: Agency Information Collection Activities; Proposals, Submissions, and Approvals: Prohibited Transaction Class Exemption for Certain Transactions between Investment Companies and Employee Benefit Plans</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/DOL_FRDOC_0001-2610</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-18T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Department of Labor (DOL) is submitting this Employee Benefits Security Administration (EBSA)-sponsored information collection request (ICR) to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and approval in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995 (PRA). Public comments on the ICR are invited.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/DOL_FRDOC_0001-2610"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">DOL_FRDOC_0001-2610</guid></item><item><title>NHTSA: The Safer Affordable Fuel-Efficient Vehicles Rule III for Model Years 2022 to 2031 Passenger Cars and Light Trucks</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/NHTSA-2025-0491-4837</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-05T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;NHTSA is announcing a 15-day extension of the comment period for the proposed rule entitled The Safer Affordable Fuel-Efficient (SAFE) Vehicles Rule III for Model Years 2022 to 2031 Passenger Cars and Light Trucks, published in the December 5, 2025 issue of the Federal Register. NHTSA is also extending the comment period for the Draft Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement (Draft SEIS) that accompanies the proposed rule. The comment period was to end on January 20, 2026 (45 days after publication of the proposed rule in the Federal Register). This document extends the comment period to February 4 to allow the public additional time to comment on the proposed rule. NHTSA is denying requests for additional public hearings based on the number of testifiers that signed up to testify for NHTSA's virtual public hearing, which was announced via Federal Register notice on December 12, 2025 and held on January 7, 2026.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/NHTSA-2025-0491-4837"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">NHTSA-2025-0491-4837</guid></item><item><title>NHTSA: The Safer Affordable Fuel-Efficient Vehicles Rule III for Model Years 2022 to 2031 Passenger Cars and Light Trucks</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/NHTSA-2025-0490-0019</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-05T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;NHTSA is announcing a 15-day extension of the comment period for the proposed rule entitled The Safer Affordable Fuel-Efficient (SAFE) Vehicles Rule III for Model Years 2022 to 2031 Passenger Cars and Light Trucks, published in the December 5, 2025 issue of the Federal Register. NHTSA is also extending the comment period for the Draft Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement (Draft SEIS) that accompanies the proposed rule. The comment period was to end on January 20, 2026 (45 days after publication of the proposed rule in the Federal Register). This document extends the comment period to February 4 to allow the public additional time to comment on the proposed rule. NHTSA is denying requests for additional public hearings based on the number of testifiers that signed up to testify for NHTSA's virtual public hearing, which was announced via Federal Register notice on December 12, 2025 and held on January 7, 2026.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/NHTSA-2025-0490-0019"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">NHTSA-2025-0490-0019</guid></item><item><title>PHMSA: Hazardous Materials: Applications for Modification to Special Permits</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/PHMSA-2013-0008-0640</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-03T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In accordance with the procedures governing the application for, and the processing of, special permits from the Department of Transportation's Hazardous Material Regulations, notice is hereby given that the Office of Hazardous Materials Safety has received the application described herein.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/PHMSA-2013-0008-0640"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">PHMSA-2013-0008-0640</guid></item><item><title>CMS: CMS-10906 (Provider Directory Data for Medicare Plan Finder)</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/CMS-2026-0067-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-24T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services (CMS) is announcing an opportunity for the public to comment on CMS' intention to collect information from the public. Under the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995 (PRA), federal agencies are required to publish notice in the Federal Register concerning each proposed collection of information (including each proposed extension or reinstatement of an existing collection of information) and to allow 60 days for public comment on the proposed action. Interested persons are invited to send comments regarding our burden estimates or any other aspect of this collection of information, including the necessity and utility of the proposed information collection for the proper performance of the agency's functions, the accuracy of the estimated burden, ways to enhance the quality, utility, and clarity of the information to be collected, and the use of automated collection techniques or other forms of information technology to minimize the information collection burden.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/CMS-2026-0067-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">CMS-2026-0067-0001</guid></item><item><title>EPA: Clean Water Standards - PFAS Regulations (Updated)</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA-HQ-OW-2024-0123</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-17&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Proposed standards for PFAS chemicals in drinking water systems - UPDATED&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/EPA-HQ-OW-2024-0123"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">EPA-HQ-OW-2024-0123</guid></item><item><title>ATSDR: 2025-23599</title><link>https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ATSDR-2025-0001-0001</link><description>
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comment Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-02-24T04:59:59Z&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/commenton/ATSDR-2025-0001-0001"&gt;Submit Comment →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </description><guid isPermaLink="false">ATSDR-2025-0001-0001</guid></item></channel></rss>